Guide to the Class of 1915, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Class of 1915, Yale College, records
1914-1986
RU 493
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2
The records consist of correspondence, clippings, printed materials, and memorabilia documenting the members of the Yale College Class of 1915.
Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1915
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 10-A (YRG 10-A), Records of Yale College classes.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, clippings, printed materials, and memorabilia documenting the members of the Yale College Class of 1915.
Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1915; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae
- Records, 1914-1986; Accession 1988-A-108
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2021
  - Acheson, Dean (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Badger, Philip (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bangs, Francis H. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Beckert, Carl R. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Brice, Arthur T. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Davenport, Stephen R. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Davie, Maurice R. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fisher, Sidney (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Fisken, A. D. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Flynn, Streeter (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Galbreath, Thomas M. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Gordon, Archibald (Box 1, Folder 12 - 13)
  - Grinnell, Robert L. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Hanes, John W. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Herman, John (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Holden, William H. T. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Hunt, Carlton C. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Hyatt, I. Robert (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Jerome, Edward (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Johnson, Kenneth C. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Levin, Hyman (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Lewis, Sydney S. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Lightner, Theodore A. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Macdonald, Ranald H. (Box 2, Folder 25 - 26)
  - MacLeish, Archibald (Box 2, Folder 27 - 30)
  - Marache, Herbert W. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Mathews, Robert E. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Means, Paul (Box 2, Folder 33 - 34)
  - Meyer, Frederick W. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Moore, Douglas Stuart (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Morse, Huntington (Box 2, Folder 37 - 38)
  - Offutt, Casper Y. (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Outhwaite, Leonard (Box 3, Folder 40 - 41)
  - Palmer, Edward L. (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Podoloff, Jacob (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Rivers, Francis E. (Box 3, Folder 44 - 45)
  - Robb, J. Donald (Box 3, Folder 46 - 47)
  - Sherman, F. Barreda (Box 4, Folder 48 - 49)
  - Smith, Edward F. (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Smith, Everett (Box 4, Folder 51 - 52)
  - Smith, Truman (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Sosnowski, Dennis E. (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Stewart, George (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Walker, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Weissman, George (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Correspondence and papers (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Clippings (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Programs and memorabilia (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Correspondence of Class of 1915 secretary William A. Jordan, 1915, 1966-1986; Accession 1991-A-049
  - Bartlett, Robert M., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bolton, Frank A., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Coates, W. Shelby, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - English, Philip Henry, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ford, David K., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Frost, Donald Franklin, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Galbreath, Thomas M., 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Hanes, John W., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hovey, Leon B., 1967-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Kinsley, Harry, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Leete, William J., 1966-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lessey, Samuel K., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Marache, Herbert William, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Means, Paul Banwell, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Morse, Huntington T., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Ohlson, John A., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Peters, Andrew, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Robb, John Donald, Sr., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Weller, Mabel Tilton, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Class Picture, 1915 June (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)